YMCA ARMED SERVICES DEPARTMENT:
University of Minnesota Libraries
- Administrative Files
  - General Files:
    - Recommended salary program for domestic USO operations, 1971. (Box 96)
    - Salary administration, 1971. (Box 120)
    - Sampson, Major Francis L., 1972-1973. (Box 96)
    - Scrapbooks, 1943-1944. (Box 96)
    - Selective service and military training, 1926-1967. (Box 96)
    - Self-appraisal studies, 1969-1971.; 2 folders. (Box 96)
    - Service to Armed Forces Personnel, 1975-1976. (Box 96)
    - Service on college campuses, 1943-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 96)
    - Service to WAACS, WAVES, etc., 1943-1946. (Box 96)
    - Services to Negroes, 1941-1945. (Box 97)
    - Shutterbug Benny and USO in action, 1953-1961. (Box 97)
    - Signs, 1941-1944, 1950.; 2 folders. (Box 97)
    - Sivertsen, Warren, 1953-1964. (Box 97)
    - Soldier opinion about USO clubs, 1944. (Box 97)
    - Southern area, 1941-1942. (Box 120)
    - Southwest area, 1940-1941. (Box 120)
    - Speakers bureau, 1942-1945. (Box 97)
    - Staff commitments, 1944, 1975. (Box 97)
    - Staff conference, minutes, 1943-1946.; 3 folders. (Box 97)
    - Staff training, 1941-1945.; 3 folders. (Box 97)
    - Standby operations, 1945. (Box 97)
    - States, Alabama-Washington, 1940-1945.; 10 folders. (Box 120)
    - Stationary, 1941-1943. (Box 97)
    - Statistical reports, 1945-1951. (Box 97)
    - Study of needs of Armed Services personnel for continued voluntary social services, materials, 1975-1976. (Box 97)
    - Study of professional staff training needs, 1974. (Box 120)
    - Study of relationship of YMCA USO with protestant churches, 1942. (Box 97)
    - Summary of YMCA/USO operations, 1966. (Box 97)
    - Supplemental fund raising, undated. (Box 97)
    - Survey forms, undated. (Box 97)
    - Survey of voluntary civilian services for military personnel, 1962.; 2 folders. (Box 97)
    - Taxes, 1941-1942. (Box 97)
    - Taxes, California welfare exemption, 1953. (Box 97)
    - Termination, 1950. (Box 97)
    - Termination plan, 1947. (Box 97)
    - Tidball, Charles T., 1951-1960. (Box 97)
    - Training, 1944-1945. (Box 120)
    - Training conferences, 1941-1943.; 2 folders. (Box 97)
    - Transfer of operations, 1944. (Box 97)
    - Troops in transit service, 1941, 1944. (Box 97)
    - Transfer of USO clubs to YMCA, 1947-1947. (Box 97)
    - Travel itineraries, 1973-1976. (Box 97)
    - Treasury Department, 1948-1951. (Box 97)
    - United Way, 1975. (Box 97)
    - United Nations programs, 1958. (Box 120)
    - United Nations Welfare Officer for Gaza, 1959-1962.; 3 folders. (Box 97)
    - United States Air Force (USAF), campaign kit, 1950. (Box 97)
    - USAF, organization/charter, 1950. (Box 97)
    - USAF policies, 1950. (Box 97)
    - USO, 1977-1980.; 3 folders. (Box 97)
    - "USO in Action", working files, 1955-1959.; 2 folders. (Box 120)
    - USO in Central Maryland, 1974. (Box 120)
    - USO for a new military, 1973. (Box 97)
    - USO Camp Shows, Inc., reports, 1942.; 4 folders. (Box 97)
    - USO Camp Shows, Inc., reports, 1946, 1953.; 3 folders. (Box 98)
    - USO Camp Shows, Inc., general, 1942-1945.; 2 folders. (Box 98)
    - USO recreation centers, War Department data, 1941-1942.; 2 folders. (Box 98)
    - Veterans, 1940s.; 6 folders. (Box 98)
    - Victory book campaign, 1942-1943. (Box 98)
    - Vietnam discrepancies, 1972-1973.; 2 folders. (Box 98)
    - Visitation task force materials, undated. (Box 120)
    - Visits, 1966-1975. (Box 98)
    - Volunteers, 1942-1945, 1948-1953.; 2 folders. (Box 98)
    - Volunteers, 1948-1962. (Box 120)
    - Volunteers and staff, handbook, 1967. (Box 98)
    - Volunteer handbook, Wherever they Go, 1965. (Box 120)
    - Volunteers, Keeping the Vision is Supervision, undated. (Box 120)
    - Volunteer manuals, 1945-1946. (Box 120)
    - Volunteer manual, 1965.; 2 folders. (Box 98)
    - War fund campaign, undated.; 4 folders. (Box 98)
    - War production areas, 1941-1944. (Box 98)
    - Washington meeting, defense morale conference, 1941.; 2 folders. (Box 98)
    - West Central area, 1940-1941. (Box 120)
    - Women and girls programs, 1946. (Box 120)
    - Workers creed, undated. (Box 120)
    - YMCA withdrawal from USO, 1976-1977.; 6 folders. (Box 98)
    - Withdrawal of USO financial support, 1958-1962.; 2 folders. (Box 98)
    - Withdrawal of USO financial support, 1957-1960.; 5 folders. (Box 99)
    - Women and girls in industry, 1942-1945. (Box 99)
    - Women's and girls' programs, 1946. (Box 121)
    - World court questions, 1931-1935. (Box 99)
    - Work camps, 1942-1943.; 5 folders. (Box 99)
    - Work study program, 1965. (Box 99)
    - Workers creed, undated. (Box 121)
    - Youth questions, 1936-1940. (Box 99)
    - YMCA budget, 1974. (Box 99)
  - Associated Organizations:
    - Designated clubs supervised by USO organizations, 1974-1976. (Box 99)
    - American Legion, 1963. (Box 99)
    - American Red Cross, 1966-1972. (Box 99)
    - National Catholic Community Service, 1941. (Box 99)
    - National Catholic Community Service, NCCS, 1944-1947.; 3 folders. (Box 99)
    - National Catholic Community Service, publications, undated, 1955.; 5 folders. (Box 99)
    - National Jewish Welfare Board, 1942-1945.; 4 folders. (Box 99)
    - National Jewish Welfare Board, program service, 1942-1946.; 6 folders. (Box 99)
    - National Jewish Welfare Board, Sentinel, 1942-1945. (Box 100)
    - National Jewish Welfare Board, USO material, 1944. (Box 100)
    - USO material, Veterans Service Information Bulletin, 1944-1945. (Box 100)
    - National Travelers Aid Association, 1942-1945. (Box 100)
    - National Travelers Aid Association, print materials, 1940-1966. (Box 100)
    - National Travelers Aid Association, Shifting Scenes, 1942-1948. (Box 100)
    - Salvation Army, 1942-1946. (Box 100)
    - Salvation Army, printed materials, undated.; 2 folders. (Box 100)
    - Salvation Army, The Red Shield, 1942-1943. (Box 100)
    - Salvation Army, Service of the Salvation Army and Program Bulletin, 1946-1947. (Box 100)
    - Salvation Army, War Service Bulletin, 1944-1946. (Box 100)
    - YWCA, printed materials, 1941-1947.; 4 folders. (Box 100)
  - Committees, Conferences, Councils, and Boards:
    - Agency Advisory Council, 1959-1962, 1973-1976.; 13 folders. (Box 100)
    - Agency Executives for Campus Service, 1944-1946. (Box 100)
    - Armed Services Department Committee, 1953-1960. (Box 100)
    - Board of Directors, 1941-1947.; 17 folders. (Box 100)
    - Board of Directors, 1948-1957, 1968-1969, 1971-1972.; 13 folders. (Box 101)
    - Board of Governors, 1971-1972, 1975-1976.; 5 folders. (Box 101)
    - Board of Management, 1942-1947. (Box 101)
    - Board of Review, 1946-1947.; 6 folders. (Box 101)
    - Budget and Finance Committee, 1976.; 3 folders. (Box 101)
    - Committee on general policy, 1941. (Box 120)
    - Committee on Community Grants, 1943-1947.; 3 folders. (Box 101)
    - Committee on Community Organization, 1941-1945. (Box 101)
    - Committee on Coordination, 1941. (Box 101)
    - Committee on Demobilization, 1943-1944. (Box 101)
    - Committee to Develop Volunteer Service Programs, 1941-1944. (Box 101)
    - Conference of Agency Executives, 1971-1972.; 2 folders. (Box 101)
    - Conference of Agency Executives, 1973. (Box 102)
    - Conference of Comptrollers, 1944-1946, 1948-1949.; 2 folders. (Box 102)
    - Conference of Executives, 1941-1944.; 38 folders. (Box 102)
    - Conference of Executives, 1944-1950.; 26 folders. (Box 103)
    - Conference with leaders of recreation and welfare, 1941. (Box 103)
    - Executive committee, 1940-1945.; 17 folders. (Box 103)
    - Executive committee, 1944. (Box 120)
    - Executive committee, 1945-1952.; 23 folders. (Box 104)
    - Executive committee, report on ad hoc survey committee, 1961-1965.; 2 folders. (Box 104)
    - Committee on field operations, 1941-1946.; 5 folders. (Box 104)
    - Finance and executive committee, 1976.; 2 folders. (Box 104)
    - Committees, general, 1944-1948. (Box 104)
    - General commission on chaplains, 1959. (Box 104)
    - Committee on general policy, 1941. (Box 121)
    - Committee on general policy, 1941-1943.; 9 folders. (Box 104)
    - Industrial committee, 1942. (Box 104)
    - Industrial committee, 1943-1944. (Box 105)
    - Committee on insurance, 1941. (Box 105)
    - Inter-agency program committee, 1969-1974.; 4 folders. (Box 105)
    - International Committee recommendation, undated. (Box 120)
    - Joint training committee, 1943-1946.; 9 folders. (Box 105)
    - Committee lists, 1942-1947, 1961.; 3 folders. (Box 105)
    - Literature committee, 1943. (Box 105)
    - National ad hoc USO survey committee report, 1962-1963.; 2 folders. (Box 105)
    - National budget and consultation committee, 1967-1972.; 2 folders. (Box 105)
    - National council, 1956-1957.; 3 folders. (Box 105)
    - African American service committee, 1941-1945.; 2 folders. (Box 105)
    - Overseas service committee, 1942-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 105)
    - Personnel committee, 1941-1945.; 7 folders. (Box 105)
    - Personnel committee, 1945-1946, 1949.; 3 folders. (Box 106)
    - Program advisory committee, report, 1954.; 3 folders. (Box 106)
    - Program committee, 1941-1944, 1949-1950.; 2 folders. (Box 106)
    - Program committee, subcommittee on equipment, 1942-1943. (Box 106)
    - Public relations committee, 1941-1945. (Box 106)
    - Publicity council, 1949. (Box 106)
    - Committee on records and reporting, 1941-1944.; 4 folders. (Box 106)
    - Regional staff conference, 1942. (Box 120)
    - Religious literature committee, 1973. (Box 120)
    - Committee on renovations and rentals, 1941. (Box 106)
    - Committee on research and studies, 1944. (Box 106)
    - Committee on review of USO program, 1943-1944.; 2 folders. (Box 106)
    - Committee on service reports, 1943-1947.; 3 folders. (Box 106)
    - Committee on services to Negroes, 1945-1948. (Box 106)
    - Committee on services in war production communities, 1944-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 106)
    - Committee on service to women and girls, 1942-1946.; 9 folders. (Box 106)
    - Snack bar committee, 1942. (Box 106)
    - Committee on staff development, 1946. (Box 106)
    - Staff development conference, 1952. (Box 120)
    - Study committee, report, 1959. (Box 106)
    - Study committee, status, 1973-1974. (Box 106)
    - Study committee on relocation, 1975-1976. (Box 106)
    - Committee to study services in communities adjacent to military hospitals, 1944-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 106)
    - Transit service committee, 1941-1944.; 2 folders. (Box 107)
    - United national welfare committee, 1940-1941. (Box 107)
    - Committee on volunteer services, 1944-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 107)
    - Committee on war production services, 1944.; 3 folders. (Box 107)
    - Sub-committee on joint training, 1942-1943. (Box 107)
  - History:
    - Historical background, 1950-1976. (Box 107)
    - History, 1942-1947.; 3 folders. (Box 107)
    - History of USO, 1947.; 15 folders. (Box 107)
    - History, 1950-1974.; 2 folders. (Box 107)
    - History, Julia Carson correspondence, 1944-1946. (Box 107)
    - History of USO in Panama, 1948. (Box 121)
  - Jay Urice Files:
    Jay Urice worked with the War Work Council from 1917-1920. He later became the associate general secretary of the National Council, a position he held from 1934-1954; it was in this capacity that he played an integral part in the establishment of the YMCA USO.
    - General files, 1939-1949.; 8 folders. (Box 121)
    - Correspondence, general, 1940-1941.; 4 folders. (Box 107)
    - Correspondence, general, 1941-1942.; 24 folders. (Box 108)
    - Accounting committee, 1941-1942. (Box 108)
    - Budgets, 1941-1943.; 3 folders. (Box 108)
    - Budget planning committee, 1941. (Box 108)
    - Building committee, 1941-1942. (Box 108)
    - Buildings, 1941-1942.; 2 folders. (Box 108)
    - Buildings, 1943-1945. (Box 109)
    - Building services division, 1944-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 109)
    - Bulletin, 1942-1949. (Box 109)
    - Bulletin, Women's division, 1941-1944. (Box 109)
    - Camp shows, 1942-1947.; 2 folders. (Box 109)
    - Campaign, 1941-1942, 1946.; 8 folders. (Box 109)
    - Certificates of recognition committee, 1943-1945. (Box 109)
    - Chairmen, 1942-1946.; 3 folders. (Box 109)
    - Charges for services, 1941, 1944. (Box 109)
    - Church relations, 1941-1944.; 5 folders. (Box 109)
    - Citizens committee, 1942. (Box 109)
    - Clubs, 1943-1946.; 2 folders. (Box 109)
    - Correspondence and papers, 1943-1945.; 8 folders. (Box 109)
    - Correspondence and papers, 1946-1947.; 4 folders. (Box 110)
    - Miscellaneous, 1943-1947. (Box 110)
    - Executive committee, 1954-1962.; 5 folders. (Box 110)
  - Charles Wharton Files:
    - Action newsletter, 1944-1945. (Box 110)
    - Bear Mountain conference, 1945.; 2 folders. (Box 110)
    - Budget material, 1943-1945. (Box 110)
    - Buildings and equipment, 1941-1943. (Box 110)
    - Industrial conferences, 1943-1945. (Box 110)
    - Operations statistics, 1944-1945. (Box 110)
    - Participation statistics, 1945. (Box 110)
    - Personnel, A-Z, 1943-1946.; 7 folders. (Box 110)
    - Personnel statistics, 1941-1946. (Box 110)
    - Program material, 1942-1944.; 4 folders. (Box 110)
    - Annual reports, 1942. (Box 110)
    - Tri-annual reports, 1943-1944.; 3 folders. (Box 110)
    - Tri-annual reports, 1944-1946.; 4 folders. (Box 111)
    - What's Doing, excerpts, 1944-1945. (Box 111)
    - When Millions Migrate, background materials, 1945-1946. (Box 111)
  - Local Club Files:
    Miscellaneous records, including clippings, reports, audits, and minutes, generated by individual USO clubs and subsequently transferred to the national office after the clubs were closed.
    - Ozark, AL, directory of local services, 1943. (Box 121)
    - Selma, AL, reports and correspondence, 1949-1964. (Box 111)
    - Fairbanks, AK, 1948-1975.; 2 folders. (Box 111)
    - Fairbanks, AK, closing program, 1947. (Box 121)
    - Fort Smith, AR, 1946-1959.; 5 folders. (Box 111)
    - Fort Smith, AR, annual report, 1944. (Box 121)
    - Fort Smith, AR, 9th Street USO, 1953-1958. (Box 111)
    - Fairfield, CA, 1950-1959.; 5 folders. (Box 111)
    - Los Angeles, CA, 1973. (Box 111)
    - Monterey, CA, programs, 1952, 1964. (Box 121)
    - Oceanside, CA, 1947-1963.; 5 folders. (Box 111)
    - Oceanside, CA, operating committee minutes, 1955-1959.; 2 folders. (Box 111)
    - Oceanside, CA, narrative report, 1961. (Box 111)
    - Oceanside, CA, programming, 1961, 1964. (Box 111)
    - Orange County, CA, survey, 1968. (Box 111)
    - Oxnard, CA, report of visitation task force, 1970. (Box 111)
    - San Francisco, Buchanan St. volunteer graduation program, 1945. (Box 121)
    - San Bernadino, CA, photographs, undated. (Box 111)
    - San Francisco, CA, 1968-1974.; 2 folders. (Box 111)
    - San Pedro, CA, reports and correspondence, 1924-1954. (Box 111)
    - Santa Maria, CA, 1950-1953. (Box 111)
    - Twenty Nine Palms, CA, 1973-1975. (Box 111)
    - Vallejo, CA, monthly statistics, 1943-1946. (Box 111)
    - Victorville, CA, area inventory, 1966. (Box 111)
    - Victorville, CA, USO budget, 1967-1973. (Box 111)
    - Victorville, CA, correspondence, 1966-1972. (Box 111)
    - Victorville, CA, correspondence, building and lease, 1967-1973. (Box 111)
    - Victorville, CA, council minutes and by-laws, 1967-1973. (Box 111)
    - Victorville, CA, council roster, 1967-1969. (Box 111)
    - Victorville, CA, designated center, 1973-1974. (Box 111)
    - Victorville, CA, miscellaneous, 1966. (Box 111)
    - Victorville, CA, narrative reports, 1967-1973.; 3 folders. (Box 111)
    - Victorville, CA, opening, 1966-1967. (Box 112)
    - Victorville, CA, program and publicity, 1967. (Box 112)
    - New London, CT, volunteer training institute, program, 1944. (Box 121)
    - Fort Walton Beach, FL, 1955-1957.; 2 folders. (Box 112)
    - Fort Walton Beach, FL, committee of management, 1952-1955. (Box 112)
    - Fort Walton Beach, FL, programming, 1961. (Box 112)
    - Fort Walton Beach, FL, MCD, 1952-1955, 1960-1963.; 2 folders. (Box 112)
    - Key West, FL, 1956-1959, 1963-1970.; 6 folders. (Box 112)
    - Key West, FL, clippings, 1952-1958, 1961-1963.; 3 folders. (Box 112)
    - Key West, FL, materials, 1964. (Box 112)
    - Key West, FL, committee of management, 1950-1959.; 4 folders. (Box 112)
    - Key West, FL, reports and correspondence, 1946-1963.; 6 folders. (Box 112)
    - Milton, FL, financial statements, 1964. (Box 121)
    - Orlando, FL, 1972. (Box 112)
    - Pensacola, FL, 1946-1966.; 10 folders. (Box 112)
    - Pensacola, FL, financial statements, 1962, 1964. (Box 121)
    - Pensacola, FL, Girls Service Organization manual, 1962. (Box 112)
    - Pensacola, FL, informational brochure, undated. (Box 121)
    - Albany, GA, 1976. (Box 112)
    - Atlanta, GA, self-appraisal study, 1970. (Box 112)
    - Augusta, GA, programs, 1944. (Box 121)
    - Columbus, GA, financial statements, 1962-1964. (Box 121)
    - Columbus, GA, African American branch, 1949-1963. (Box 112)
    - Valdosta, GA, 1952-1959, 1976.; 2 folders. (Box 112)
    - Warner Robins, GA, monthly statistics, 1944-1946. (Box 112)
    - Rantoul, IL, 1963-1966.; 3 folders. (Box 112)
    - Rantoul, IL, clippings, 1952-1957, 1960-1962.; 6 folders. (Box 112)
    - Rantoul, IL, programs, 1952, 1955, 1959. (Box 121)
    - Rantoul, IL, reports and correspondence, 1940-1962.; 3 folders. (Box 113)
    - Waukegan, IL, 1947-1949. (Box 113)
    - Franklin, IN, volunteer training course, program, 1944. (Box 121)
    - Junction City, KS, reports and correspondence, 1948-1953. (Box 113)
    - Elizabethtown, KY, USO course, program, 1945. (Box 121)
    - Hopkinsville, KY, volunteer conference program, 1944. (Box 121)
    - Leesville, LA, 1941-1945, 1950-1959.; 3 folders. (Box 113)
    - New Orleans, LA, 1970. (Box 113)
    - Ayer, MA, locator service manual, 1944. (Box 121)
    - Ayer, MA, recognition banquet program, 1956. (Box 113)
    - Detroit, MI, self-appraisal study, 1970.; 2 folders. (Box 113)
    - Saulte Ste Marie, MI, 1961-1962. (Box 113)
    - Hattiesburg, MS, program report, 1944. (Box 124)
    - Meridian, MS, program report, 1944. (Box 124)
    - Fort Leonard Wood, MO, 1950-1951. (Box 113)
    - St. Louis, MO, visitation task force report, 1970. (Box 113)
    - Reno, NV, 1958-1962. (Box 113)
    - Reno, NV, financial statements, 1961-1962. (Box 122)
    - Reno, NV, reports and correspondence, 1951-1958. (Box 113)
    - New Hampshire USOs, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Portsmouth, NH, operating committee, 1971-1973. (Box 113)
    - Eatontown, NJ, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Fort Dix, NJ, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Lakehurst, NJ, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Long Branch, NJ, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Red Bank, NJ, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Alamogordo, NM, 1952-1954. (Box 113)
    - Fort Hamilton, NY, financial statements, 1953-1958. (Box 122)
    - Fort Slocum, NY, news, 1921. (Box 122)
    - Fort Totten, NY, financial statements, 1966-1967. (Box 122)
    - Hempstead, NY, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - New York City, Harbor Club, 1944-1959.; 4 folders. (Box 113)
    - Oswego, NY, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Rochester, NY, financial statements, 1956-1963. (Box 122)
    - Rome, NY, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Sidney, NY, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Watertown, NY, audit, 1942. (Box 124)
    - Durham, NC, volunteer training, 1944. (Box 122)
    - Fayetteville, NC, 1975-1976. (Box 113)
    - Fayetteville, NC, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Fayetteville, NC, programs, 1943-1945. (Box 122)
    - Jacksonville, NC, 1950-1959, 1976.; 6 folders. (Box 113)
    - Jacksonville, NC, minutes and insurance, 1976. (Box 113)
    - Kinston, NC, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Morehead City, NC, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Spring Lake/Manchester, NC, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Swansboro, NC, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Wilmington, NC, 1951-1959.; 3 folders. (Box 113)
    - Wilmington, NC, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Minot, ND, 1964-1976.; 6 folders. (Box 113)
    - Minot, ND, budget and finance, 1966-1967. (Box 113)
    - Minot, ND, insurance, 1965-1974. (Box 113)
    - Minot, ND, lease agreements, 1963-1964. (Box 113)
    - Minot, ND, self-appraisal study, 1970-1971. (Box 113)
    - Minot, ND, visitation task force, 1970. (Box 113)
    - Ravenna, OH, audit, 1942. (Box 124)
    - Lawton, OK, 1950-1959.; 3 folders. (Box 113)
    - Lawton, OK, 1954-1967.; 5 folders. (Box 114)
    - Lawton, OK, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Lawton, OK, clippings, 1958-1965.; 2 folders. (Box 114)
    - Lawton, OK, coronation ball program, 1958. (Box 114)
    - Lawton, OK, narrative report, 1959. (Box 122)
    - Lawton, OK, operating committee, 1950-1959.; 3 folders. (Box 114)
    - Lawton, OK, Operation Mad Ball, publicity, 1957. (Box 122)
    - Norman, OK, manual, 1943. (Box 122)
    - Astoria, OR, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Pendleton, OR, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Chester, PA, audit, 1942. (Box 124)
    - Harrisburg, PA, audit, 1942. (Box 124)
    - Lebanon, PA, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Middletown, PA, audit, 1942. (Box 124)
    - Philadelphia, PA, photographs, undated. (Box 114)
    - Philadelphia, PA, visitation task force, 1972. (Box 114)
    - Pittsburgh, PA, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Jamestown, RI, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Providence, RI, visitation task force, 1971. (Box 114)
    - Beaufort, SC, 1957-1961. (Box 114)
    - Charleston, SC, awards ceremony programs, 1951-1952. (Box 122)
    - Charleston, SC, staff service bulletin, 1954. (Box 122)
    - Charleston, SC, volunteer recognition program, 1945. (Box 122)
    - Columbia, SC, 1942-1975. (Box 114)
    - Columbia, SC, USO Columbia Council, Inc., 1967-1973.; 3 folders. (Box 114)
    - Charleston, SC, clippings, 1961-1962. (Box 114)
    - Spartanburg, SC, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Sumter, SC, 1948-1973.; 9 folders. (Box 114)
    - Fort Sumter, SC, closing, 1970-1974.; 2 folders. (Box 114)
    - Fort Sumter, SC, leases, contracts, 1948-1968. (Box 114)
    - Rapid City, SD, reports and correspondence, 1948-1962.; 3 folders. (Box 114)
    - Clarksville, TN, 1950-1971.; 4 folders. (Box 114)
    - Clarksville, TN, clippings, 1955-1963, 1971.; 5 folders. (Box 114)
    - Clarksville, TN, statistical report, 1980. (Box 114)
    - Clarksville, TN, volunteer recognition dinner, program, 1954. (Box 122)
    - Memphis, TN, audit, 1942. (Box 124)
    - Paris, TN, audit, 1942. (Box 124)
    - Tullahoma, TN, audit, 1942. (Box 124)
    - Abilene, TX, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Austin, TX, 1973. (Box 114)
    - Bay City, TX, audit, 1942. (Box 124)
    - Brownsville, TX, audit, 1942. (Box 124)
    - Brownwood, TX, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Corpus Christi, TX, audit, 1942. (Box 124)
    - Dallas, TX, 1953-1961, 1971-1975.; 2 folders. (Box 114)
    - Dallas, TX, insurance, 1958-1973. (Box 114)
    - Dallas, TX, USO council, 1968-1973. (Box 114)
    - Fort Hood, TX, 1966. (Box 115)
    - Galveston, TX, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Houston, TX, 1969-1974. (Box 115)
    - Houston, TX, Angels with Armbands Volunteers, undated. (Box 115)
    - Houston, TX, audit, 1942. (Box 124)
    - Houston, TX, minutes, 1969-1973. (Box 115)
    - Mineral Wells, TX, audits, 1942. (Box 124)
    - Orange, TX, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - San Antonio, TX, 1967-1971. (Box 115)
    - San Antonio, TX, audit, 1942. (Box 124)
    - San Antonio, TX, financial statements, 1964. (Box 122)
    - San Antonio, TX, scrapbook, 1942.; 2 folders. (Box 115)
    - San Antonio, TX, reports and correspondence, 1948-1960.; 2 folders. (Box 115)
    - Sherman, TX, 1963-1970.; 3 folders. (Box 115)
    - Sherman, TX, financial statements, 1964, 1967. (Box 122)
    - Temple, TX, 1947-1973.; 4 folders. (Box 115)
    - Temple, TX, agreements, 1950-1972.; 2 folders. (Box 115)
    - Temple, TX, audit, 1942. (Box 122)
    - Temple, TX, closing, 1973.; 2 folders. (Box 115)